ACTWU's Textile Division Records 5619/038
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Textile Division Records
1945-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Textile Division
Textile Workers' Union of America. Textile Division
5619/038
21 cubic feet
21 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of reports, files, and correspondence of the Textile Divisions of Textile Workers' Union of America and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union.
6826803
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
March 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, July 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America And all other 5619 collections.
Textile industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Textile Division; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Textile Workers Union of America; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6826803
- ACTWU Initiation Fee Waivers, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Knitting Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Carpet, Knitting, Rope & Cordage Industry Conference, March 14-15. Washington., D.C., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ACTWU - GEB -- Communications from four Officers, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Knitting & Carpet Conferences. Nov 4-6, NYC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Knitting Industry - Bruce Dunton, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Knitting Industry - Data & Surveys, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Knitting Industry. Dick Plescia, Dir. General, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- TWUA Knit Plants - Old, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ACTWU Legal Dept, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Textile Mill Liquidations, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Legal Dept., 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ACTWU Legislative & Political Education Dept., 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ACTWU Political Action Committee and Political Education Fund, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Cope Report, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Political and Legislative. October 19, Memo to Regional Directors on PAC Receipts, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Sol Stetin - Mailings, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Sol Stetin - Mailings, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ACTWU Managerial Rebates, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ACTWU Managerial Rebate Central Alabama Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- ACTWU Manager's Rebate - GTA Joint Board, 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ACTWU Managerial Rebates - Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- ACTWU Manager's Rebate - Toronto Joint Board, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ACTWU Managerial Rebates Textile Division, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- ACTWU Managerial Rebates, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- ACTWU Managerial Rebates, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ACTWU Managerial Rebates, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- TWUA Joint Boards Managerial Rebates, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Organizing Department. (Textile Division), 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- George Perkel - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Research Reports - Textile Division, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Organizing, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Jack Sheinkman, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Textile Division/Organizing, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Organizing Department, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- ACTWU - Shoe Division affiliated February, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Banking (Speech), 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Banking and Corporation Articles (Taken from 4/17/80 BBD File), 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Corporate Power, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ACTWU -- New Charters, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Charters (Before the merge 3/69-4/70), 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Charter Info/Materials - Inactive Locals, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Communications, Director Burt Beck, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Dyers Division, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Dyers Policy Committee. Lyndhurst, NJ. July 23., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Dyers Division - Sp. Meeting. 15 Union Square. Mon. Nov 22, 11A.M., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Mid-Atlantic Dyers, Finishers Labor-Management Conference. Lyndhurst, NJ. Wed., April 28., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Dyers Division - Mid Atlantic Trustees. 15 Union Square. November 23. 11:00 AM, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Dyers Leadership Meeting. NYC. Thursday, May 15., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Dyers Negotiations. September 10, 15, 24, 25, 26, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Dyers Division. New England Dyers Pattern Locals meeting. Providence, RI. June 20., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Dyers Meeting. Paterson, NJ. Local 1733. Nov 14, 10 AM., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Dyers Negotiating Meeting. Lyndhurst, NJ. August 13., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- ACTWU Dye & Machine Contract (Oct. 16 - Oct. 1), 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Dyers' Strike & Settlement (NY-NJ Metro. Area.), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Dyers Contract (10/5/74-10/1/77 - Extended), 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Signing of Dyers Extension. April 5, 20 SM, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Dyers Contract File Copy, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Dyers - Sub-file - & has received files, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Dyers Negotiations, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Dyers Division - Meeting of Fulltime Representatives Dec. 17, 9:30 AM 770 Bwy, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund - Investment Committee, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Textile Workers Pension Plan, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Wolkow, Wasyl (CESO), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Mid-Atlantic Pension Plan Actuaries Studies, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund - Regional List of Companies in Pension Plant, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Investment Performance Report - Feb. 1976 thru Feb. 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund - 99 University, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1967-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- TWUA Welfare Fund Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Thursday, December 16, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Auditor's Report 9/3/82 (Dist. At Meeting 12/16/82), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Minutes of Tex. Workers Pension Fund Meeting - 9/22/82, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Personnel Committee. Dec 15, 4 PM, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Wed., Dec - 1, 99 University. Investment Committee, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Minutes of Investment Committee Meeting - Sept. 9, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Wednesday, June 16., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund - Investment Committee Thurs., Sept. 9, 10:30 AM, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund - Investment Committee. June 16, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Wednesday, March 24, 10:00 Trustees Meet …Lunch, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Thursday, December 10. 10:00 AM, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Pension Fund, Bd. Of Trustees. Wed. 9-23-81 99 University PL., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Board of Trustees. June 23, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. 99 University. Tuesday May 19, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. April. 8, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, Luchows. Thursday, Dec. 18, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. NYC. Oct, 15, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. NYC. July 24, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. NYC. May 15, 10 AM. Lunch, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Health, Welfare and Pension Plans Educational Conference. Palm Springs, CA. March 16-20, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Dec. 18, 10 AM Feathers, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Board of Trustees. NYC. Oct. 4, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Board of Trustees. NYC. July 19, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Board of Trustees - April 3, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- TWUA Pension Fund Annual Lunch. Fifth Ave. Hotel. December 18. 12:45, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- TWUA Pension Fun Meeting, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Trustees - T.W. Pension Plan Mtg. Followed by Luncheon - Delfino's. Sept. 29, (Thurs). 10:00 a.m., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- TWUA Pension Fund (Trustees) N.Y.C. Deathers. June 27, 1 PM., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. University P. 12 - Feathers April 6, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- National. Pension Fund Participants (Union reps. Servicing) NYC Board Room Mar. 27, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- TWUA Pension Fund Meeting 10:00 AM. Board rm. Lunch at Feathers Dec. 19th, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Trustees Meeting. June 28, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Meeting, called by Sol Stetin, for Union Representatives Servicing Participants of the Nat. Pension Plan. June 27., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Trustees Meeting - June 1, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund Trustees Meeting - March 30, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. December 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. Trustees Meeting - Sept. 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- TWUA Pension Fund - Minutes June 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Transfile # 144 J.P. Stevens, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- JPS Rothstein, Richard, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- JPS Rothstein, Richard (4/2/79-5/25/79), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- JPS Rothstein, Richard, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens Stockholders Meeting, (H. Brown) Greenville, SC. March 6, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- JPS Stockholders Meeting 3/7/78, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- JPS - Southern Exposure Magazine, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens - Union Issues, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- JPS Boycott - Senior Citizens, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- JP Stevens Shareholders Meeting. Greenville, S.C. 3-7-78, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- JPS Shareholders Meeting, Strategy, etc. March 6., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- JPS Social Justice, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- JPS Social Services, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- JPS Bill Somplatsky - Jarman, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- JPS Settlement Rumors, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- JPS. Southerners for Economic Justice, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- J.P.S. Ohio - Federated Campaign Letter to AFL-CIO Presidents from Sol Stetin (4/27/79), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- JPS Thompson Reports on Stevens Meetings, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- JP Stevens - Testimony Quebec June 7, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- JPS Stores Gimbels, NYC, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- JPS Shareholder's Meeting. March 4, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- JPS Sheinkman, Reports to Jack Sheinkman, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- JPS Boycott Stores Gimbels - Paramus N.J., 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- JPS Macy's "Boycott", 1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- JPS F.W. Woolworth Co., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- JPS Supporters of Boycott, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- JPS Supporters of Boycott, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- JSP Worker - to - Workers Program, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Southerners for Economic Justice (Bd. Mtg.) Atlanta, GA. Fri. May 16, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Federated (Boycott) Campaign Stores March 30, Cleveland, Ohio, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- JPS Letters to ACTWU to support boycott and responses, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- JPS Support NY State Democratic Commission and Democratic Conference, Memphis, TN, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- JPS Amalgamated Meatcutters & Butcher Workmen of North America, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- JPS Table Cloth Problems, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- JPS Textile Labor TWUA Member March, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- JPS NAACP Testimony Film, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- JPS NAACP Corona East Elmhurst Br. Testimony Presentation, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- JPS Bronx Branch, NAACP Testimony, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- JPS Supporters New Democratic Club Testimony Showing - Jan., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Canadian Premier of Testimony - Toronto, Canada. January 31, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- JPS Textile World (Meany Statement), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- JPS Corporate, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- JPS Union Label Dept - ACTWU, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Worker Compensation - JPS 'The Russian Connection', 1978 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- JPS Wagram Plant, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- JPS Testimony Film, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- JPS "Textile Labor" NLRB Election, 1945-1975 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- JPS West Boylston Plant injury of Richard Lewis, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- JPS Westfield, N.C. Case, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- JPS - Booklet Your Best Protection (March), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- JPS Zayre Corporation (Boycott Campaign), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Complaints, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Briggs, Beverly Complaint (December), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Complaint: Central Alabama Georgia Joint Board v. Merle Charles, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- J. Wojciechowski - Complaint, Chicago Joint Board, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Complaint of Shirley Files, Local 36, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Complaint Local 66 Election (Minneapolis, MN - Hearing of files?, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Complaint of C.J, Osman, Local 66 Twin City Joint Board, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Complaint Local 933T of Jose Rosas, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Complaint Local 1034 Election Protest, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Complaint Local 1460 Morin Alice, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Complaint Local 1553, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Complaint Local 1665 Fairtex, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Complaint Local 1716 Ruth Knowles, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Complaint Local 1726 Chicago Joint Boards, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Complaint Local 1737 - Charges, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Complaint Local 1742 - Bruce Raynor, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Complaint Local 1785(T) - George Stencovage Craftex Mills, Inc. DVJB, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Complaint Local 1874(T): William Currence - Cumberland, Md., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Complaint Local 2298 - Tressie Sargent, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Complaints, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Complaint Local 77A - John Lombardo - North Jersey Joint Board, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Complaint - Tidewater Joint board, Farm Ville, VA, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Complaint Local 120T - Nelson, Dorothy - Waterville, ME, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Complaint Local 188T - Michael Rowan - Washougal, Washington., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Complaint Local 710 - Rock Hill, SC - Petition to remove James Renfroe, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Complaint Local 1373 Edith Torres (Allen Industries) L.A., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Complaint Local 1495 - John Fitch (Stearns & Foster) Lockland, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Complaint Local 1551 - Tubbs Cordage Co., Dos Palos, CA, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Complaint Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Complaint Rust, Richard .A., Southern New England Joint Board, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Complaint Tidewater Joint Board from Roger Dove, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Complaint Local 21 Xenia, Ohio Ann McDufford, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Complaint Local 254. Crisp, Dennis, Columbia SC, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Complaint Local 77 Attilio Carbone Consolidated Bleaching, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Complaint Local 375-T: Bernice White, St Louis, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Complaint Local 658-T (W. Byron Co) Mrs. Wava Barker, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Complaint Local 658. Thelma Naile - Williamsport, MD., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Complaint Local 710 Ellison vs Rock Hill Prtg., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Complaint Local 748. Frank Kasowski, Houston TX., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Complaint Local 1148 Kurtz, Christine. Stowe, PA, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Complaint Local 1371 Marie Cusanelli - Guild, N.H., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Complaint Local 1374 Helen Russell- RE: Allen Industries, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Complaint Local 1445. R. Ducharme, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Complaint Local 1445. John A. Liberto, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Complaint Local 1445 James M. Adams. Bangot, PA., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Complaint Local 1465 Maintenance Workers Courtauld, Mobile, ALA, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Complaint Local 1495 - Janet Randolph Faye Roy. Stearns & Foster - Cincinnati, Ohio, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Complaint Local 1557- Dorothy Lahey. Batavia, Ill., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Complaint Local 1604. Canton, GA, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Complaint Local 1676 - Election Objections, Wilmington, NC., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Complaint Local 1870 - Ralph Contento. Palisades, NY, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Complaint Local 2268. Jockey International. Kenosha, WI, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Complaint Local 2359 0 Election. Rosman, NC, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Complaint Local 68 - Betty Denny. Joint Board Bi-County & N. Carolina, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Complaint no.54 Local 6 Lewistown, PA, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Complaint no.74 Local 21. Xenia, Ohio, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Complaint no.64 Local 35. Edward Heckman. Easton, PA., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Complaint no.70 Local 281-T. Bemis, TN, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 58)